A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, China Medical Board records, RG 4 FA114
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1913-1929; 1
  - Appropriations - Numerical, 1913-1918; 1
    - 38. U.S. Treasury Department, 1915-1918 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - 39. Charles A. Coolidge, 1916-1917 (Box 10, Folder 128)
      P. U. M. C. Building Report
    - 40. Franklin C. McLean, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - 42. Frank D. Gamewell, 1914-1918 (Box 10, Folder 130)
      Textbook, statistics
    - 43. Mission Societies, 1914-1918 (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - 43. Mission Societies - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - 43.1 Mission Societies - Reports (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - 44. Yuan Hung Li, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 134)
      Political situation
    - 46. Textbooks, 1914-1918 (Box 10, Folder 135)
      Translations, nursing, medicine, dictionaries of medical terminology.
    - 46. Textbooks, 1914-1918 (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - 46. Textbooks, 1914-1918 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    - 50. Methodist Episcopal Church, Board of Foreign Missions (North), 1914-1918 (Box 11, Folder 138)
      Frank North Mason, George Heber Jones
    - 50. Methodist Episcopal Church, Board of Foreign Missions (North), 1914-1918 (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - 50. Methodist Episcopal Church, Board of Foreign Missions (North), 1914-1918 (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - 50.1 Applications, 1915-1918 (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - 50.1 Applications, 1915-1918 (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - 50.3 N. S. Hopkins, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 143)
    - 50.4 J. G. Vaughn, 1916-1917 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - 50.5 J. E. Skinner, 1916-1917 (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - 50.6 John H. Korns, 1917-1918 (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - 50.7 E. M. Johnstone, 1917-1918 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - 50.8 Emma Robbins (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - 50.9 George D. Lowry, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - 50.10 Frank P. Gaunt, 1917-1918 (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - 50.11 Mabel Manderson, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - 51. Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Board of Foreign Missions (North), 1914-1917 (Box 11, Folder 152)
      Robert E. Speer, Arthur J. Brown, Stanley White
    - 51. Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Board of Foreign Missions (North), 1914-1917 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - 51. Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Board of Foreign Missions (North), 1919 (Box 12, Folder 154)
    - 51.1 Applications, 1915-18 (Box 12, Folder 155)
    - 51.1 Applications, 1915-18 (Box 12, Folder 156)
    - 51.2 John R. Dickson, 1915-17 (Box 12, Folder 157)
    - 51.3 Thorton Stearns, 1914-17 (Box 12, Folder 158)
    - 51.4 John H. Wylie, 1915-17 (Box 12, Folder 159)
    - 51.5 James W. Wiltsie, 1915-18 (Box 12, Folder 160)
    - 51.7 Charles Lewis, 1915-16 (Box 12, Folder 161)
    - 51.8 William M. Schultz, 1916-17 (Box 12, Folder 162)
    - 51.9 Mr. & Mrs. Oliver T. Logan, 1914-17 (Box 12, Folder 163)
    - 51.10 Marie Rustin, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 164)
    - 51.11 Phyllis Kurtz, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 165)
    - 51.12 Martha Davis, 1916-17 (Box 12, Folder 166)
    - 51.13 Hanna Marie Fritzen, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 167)
    - 51.14 Hospital Appointments, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 168)
    - 51.15 Stephen C. Lewis, 1917-18 (Box 12, Folder 169)
    - 51.16 George T. Tootell, 1917-18 (Box 12, Folder 170)
    - 51.17 H. W. Boyd, 1917-18 (Box 12, Folder 171)
    - 52. Protestant Episcopal Church in the U.S., Domestic and Foreign Mission Society, 1914-18 (Box 12, Folder 172)
    - 52.1 Applications, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 173)
    - 52.2 Claude M. Lee, 1915-16 (Box 12, Folder 174)
    - 52.4 Mary L. James, 1917-18 (Box 12, Folder 175)
    - 52.5 Harry B. Taylor, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 176)
    - 52.6 Charles S. Lincoln, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 177)
    - 53. Reformed Church in the U.S., Board of Foreign Missions (German), 1914 (Box 12, Folder 178)
    - 54. Reformed Church in America, Board of Foreign Missions (Dutch), 1914-17 (Box 12, Folder 179)
    - 55. Foreign Christian Missionary Society (Disciples), 1914-18 (Box 12, Folder 180)
      Stephen Corey
    - 55.1 Applications, 1915 (Box 12, Folder 181)
    - 55.1 Applications, 1916-18 (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - 55.1 Applications, 1916-18 (Box 13, Folder 183)
    - 55.2 G. J. P. Barger, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 184)
    - 55.3 Jeanette Price, 1915-16 (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - 55.4 Lillian D. Robinson, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 186)
    - 55.5 Elliott I. Osgood, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 187)
    - 55.6 Lloyd R. Boutwell, 1917-18 (Box 13, Folder 188)
    - 55.7 Paul Wakefield, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 189)
    - 56. American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions, 1914-18 (Box 13, Folder 190)
      William E. Strong, James L. Barton
    - 56. American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions, 1914-18 (Box 13, Folder 191)
    - 56.1 Applications, 1915-18 (Box 13, Folder 192)
    - 56.2 Amy A. Metcalf, 1915-16 (Box 13, Folder 193)
    - 56.3 Lee M. Miles, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 194)
    - 56.4 Francis F. Tucker, 1917-18 (Box 13, Folder 195)
    - 56.5 O. Houghton Love, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 196)
    - 57. Baptist Missionary Society - London, 1914-16 (Box 13, Folder 197)
      R. Fletcher Moorshead
    - 58. Church of Scotland, Foreign Mission Committee, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 198)
    - 59. China Inland Mission - London, 1914-1917 (Box 13, Folder 199)
    - 60. London Missionary Society, 1914-18 (Box 13, Folder 200)
      F. H. Hawkins, Thomas Cochrane
    - 60.1 Applications, 1915-17 (Box 13, Folder 201)
    - 60.2 R. McLean Gibson, 1917-18 (Box 13, Folder 202)
    - 60.3 P. L. McAll, 1917-18 (Box 13, Folder 203)
    - 61. Presbyterian Church of England, Foreign Mission Committee, 1914-18 (Box 14, Folder 204)
    - 61.2 F. H. Hawkins, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 205)
    - 62. Presbyterian Church in Ireland, Foreign Mission, 1914-15 (Box 14, Folder 206)
    - 63. United Free Church of Scotland, Foreign Mission Committee, 1914-18 (Box 14, Folder 207)
    - 64. Church Missionary Society, London, 1914-16 (Box 14, Folder 208)
    - 64.1 Applications, 1914 (Box 14, Folder 209)
    - 65. Southern Baptist Convention, Foreign Mission Board, 1914-18 (Box 14, Folder 210)
      T. B. Ray
    - 65. Southern Baptist Convention, Foreign Mission Board, 1914-18 (Box 14, Folder 211)
    - 65.1 Applications, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 212)
    - 65.3 John T. Anderson, 1915-16 (Box 14, Folder 213)
    - 65.4 Jo Carr, 1915-16 (Box 14, Folder 214)
    - 65.5 Grace McBride, 1915-16 (Box 14, Folder 215)
    - 65.6 James M. Gaston, 1915-16 (Box 14, Folder 216)
    - 65.7 R. V. Taylor, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 217)
    - 65.8 T. W. Ayres, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 218)
    - 66. Society for the Propogation of the Gospel in Foreign Parts, 1914-16 (Box 14, Folder 219)
    - 67. Wesleyan Methodist Missionary Scoiety, London, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 220)
    - 68. Friends Foreign Mission Association, London, 1914-15 (Box 14, Folder 221)
    - 69. Friends Foreign Missionary Society of the Ohio Yearl Meeting, 1915-16 (Box 14, Folder 222)
    - 70. Board of Missionary Preparation, Interdenominational, 1915-16 (Box 14, Folder 223)
    - 71. Methodist Episcopal Church, Board of Missions (South), 1914-18 (Box 14, Folder 224)
    - 71.1 Applications, 1916-17 (Box 14, Folder 225)
    - 71.2 John A. Snell, 1915-16 (Box 14, Folder 226)
    - 71.4 Fred P. Magnet, 1915-17 (Box 14, Folder 227)
    - 71.5 Ethel Polk, 1917-18 (Box 14, Folder 228)
    - 71.6 W. H. Park, 1917-18 (Box 14, Folder 229)
    - 72. Presbyterian Church in Canada, Board of Foreign Missions, 1915-16 (Box 14, Folder 230)
    - 73. Methodist Episcopal Church, Women's Foreign Missionary Society (North), 1916 (Box 14, Folder 231)
    - 73.2 Mary Stone, 1915-16 (Box 14, Folder 232)
    - 73.3 Florence Sayles, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 233)
    - 74. American Baptist Foreign Mission Society (North), 1914-18 (Box 15, Folder 234)
      George B. Hantington, J. H. Franklin
    - 74.1 Applications, 1915-16 (Box 15, Folder 235)
    - 74.2 Nathan W. Brown, 1915-18 (Box 15, Folder 236)
    - 74.7 J. S. Grant, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 237)
    - 74.8 Charles B. Lesher, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 238)
    - 74.9 C. E. Tompkins, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 239)
    - 75. China Medical Missionary Association, 1915-17 (Box 15, Folder 240)
      Robert Beebe
    - 76. Presbyterian Church in the U.S., Executive Committee of Foreign Missions (South), 1915-18 (Box 15, Folder 241)
      S. H. Chester
    - 76.1 Applications, 1915-18 (Box 15, Folder 242)
    - 76.2 Mason P. Young, 1915-16 (Box 15, Folder 243)
    - 76.3 Allen C. Hutchinson, 1915-16 (Box 15, Folder 244)
    - 76.4 Nancy Smith Farmer, 1915-16 (Box 15, Folder 245)
    - 77. Missionary Society of the Methodist Church, Canada, 1915-18 (Box 15, Folder 246)
    - 77.1 Applications, 1917-18 (Box 15, Folder 247)
    - 77.2 Charles W. Service, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 248)
    - 78. Yale Medical College, Changsha, Hunan and Yale Foreign Missionary Society, 1914-16 (Box 15, Folder 249)
      Amos P. Wilder, Edward H. Hume; China Medical Association
    - 78. Yale Medical College, Changsha, Hunan and Yale Foreign Missionary Society, 1914-16 (Box 15, Folder 250)
    - 78. Yale Medical College, Changsha, Hunan and Yale Foreign Missionary Society, 1914-16 (Box 15, Folder 251)
    - 78. Yale Medical College, Changsha, Hunan and Yale Foreign Missionary Society, 1914-16 (Box 15, Folder 252)
    - 78. Yale Medical College, Changsha, Hunan and Yale Foreign Missionary Society, 1917-18 (Box 16, Folder 253)
    - 78. Yale Medical College, Changsha, Hunan and Yale Foreign Missionary Society, 1917-18 (Box 16, Folder 254)
    - 78.1 Applications, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 255)
    - 78.2 John G. B. Branch, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 256)
    - 78.3 Nina Gage, 1915-17 (Box 16, Folder 257)
    - 78.4 Douglas T. Davidson, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 258)
    - 78.5 James W. Williams, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 259)
    - 78.6 Robb, Frisken and Chang, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 260)
    - 78.7 Helen R. Gage, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 261)
    - 79.2 Medical Missionary Society of Canton - Joseph O. Thompson, 1915-18 (Box 16, Folder 262)
    - 79.3 Medical Missionary Society of Canton - Andrew H. Woods, 1917-18 (Box 16, Folder 263)
    - 80.1 Church of England Zenana Missionary Society - Applications, 1915-17 (Box 16, Folder 264)
    - 81. Reformed Church in the U. S., Women's Missionary Society (German), 1915-18 (Box 16, Folder 265)
    - 82. Christian Association of the university of Pennsylvania, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 266)
    - 83. Student Volunteer Movement in Foreign Missions, 1916-17 (Box 16, Folder 267)
    - 84. American Advent Mission Society Hospital - Chaohsien, Anhui, 1915-18 (Box 16, Folder 268)
    - 85. American Church Mission Hospital - Anking, Anhui, 1914-18 (Box 16, Folder 269)
    - 86. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) Hwaiyuen, Anhui, 1914-18 (Box 16, Folder 270)
    - 87. Foreign Christian Mission Hospital - Luchowfu, Anhui, 1915-18 (Box 16, Folder 271)
      Paul Wakefield, Stephen Corey
    - 88. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Wuhu, Anhui, 1914-18 (Box 16, Folder 272)
      Frank North Manson
    - 89. Chekiang Province, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 273)
    - 90. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Hangchow, Chekiang, 1914-18 (Box 17, Folder 274)
      Walter G. Hiltner, D. Duncan Main
    - 90. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Hangchow, Chekiang, 1914-18 (Box 17, Folder 275)
    - 90. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Hangchow, Chekiang, 1914-18 (Box 17, Folder 276)
    - 90. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Hangchow, Chekiang, 1914-18 (Box 17, Folder 277)
    - 91. Huchow Union Hospital - Huchow, Chekiang, 1914-18 (Box 17, Folder 278)
      O. G. Nelson, A. M. Dunlap, Methodist Episcopal Church, American Baptist, Southern Methodist
    - 91. Huchow Union Hospital - Huchow, Chekiang, 1914-18 (Box 17, Folder 279)
    - 93. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (South) - Kashing, Chekiang, 1913-16 (Box 17, Folder 280)
    - 94. American Baptist Mission Hospital (North) - Kinhwa, Chekiang, 1914-16 (Box 17, Folder 281)
    - 95. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Ningpo, Chekiang, 1915 (Box 17, Folder 282)
    - 96. American Baptist Mission Hospital (North) Ningpo, Chekiang, 1914-16 (Box 17, Folder 283)
    - 97. American Baptist Mission Hospital (North) Shaohing, Chekiang, 1914-18 (Box 17, Folder 284)
    - 98. China Ireland Mission Hospital - Taichow, Chekiang, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 285)
    - 99. Church Missionary Society Nospital - Taichow, Chekiang, 1914-16 (Box 17, Folder 286)
    - 100. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Yuyao, Checkiang, 1915 (Box 17, Folder 287)
    - 101. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Chanli, Chihli, 1914-15 (Box 17, Folder 288)
    - 102. Army Veterinary College - Paotingfu, Chihli, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 289)
      Government
    - 103. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Paotingfu, Chihli, 1914-18 (Box 17, Folder 290)
    - 104. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Peking, Chihli, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 291)
    - 105. Chihli Province, 1915 (Box 18, Folder 292)
    - 106. Presbyterian Mission Women's Hospital (North) - Peking, Chihli, 1914-15 (Box 18, Folder 293)
    - 107. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Peking, Chihlii (Box 18, Folder 294)
    - 108. North China Union College for Women and Elizabeth Sleeper Davis Memorial Hospital - Peking, Chihli, 1914-16 (Box 18, Folder 295)
      Methodist Episcopal Church, Women's Foreign Missionary Society
    - 109. American Board Mission Hospital - Peking, Chihli, 1914 (Box 18, Folder 296)
    - 110. Church of England Mission Hospital - Peking, Chihli, 1914 (Box 18, Folder 297)
      Society for the Propogation of the Gospel
    - 111. Tsing Hua College - Peking, Chihli, 1914-17 (Box 18, Folder 298)
      Y.M.C.A.
    - 112. Union Medical College - Peking, Chihli, 1914-18 (Box 18, Folder 299)
      Peking Union Medical College
    - 112.1 Applications, 1916-18 (Box 18, Folder 300)
    - 112.3 Land Purchase, 1914-18 (Box 18, Folder 301)
    - 112.3 Land Purchase, 1914-18 (Box 18, Folder 302)
    - 112.4 Staff Exchange, Budget, 1915-18 (Box 18, Folder 303)
    - 112.5 Charter, Incorporation (Box 18, Folder 304)
    - 112.6 Trustees, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 305)
    - 112.9 Local Executive Committee, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 306)
    - 112.11 Buildings and Equipment, 1914-17 (Box 18, Folder 307)
    - 112.11 Buildings and Equipment, 1914-17 (Box 18, Folder 308)
    - 112.11 Buildings and Equipment, 1914-17 (Box 18, Folder 309)
    - 112.11 Buildings and Equipment, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 310)
    - 112.11 Buildings and Equipment, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 311)
    - 112.11 Buildings and Equipment, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 312)
    - 112.11 Buildings and Equipment, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 313)
    - 112.13 A. W. Zucker, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 314)
    - 113. Hospitals and Institutions for Defectives - Peking, Chihli, 1913 (Box 19, Folder 315)
    - 114. General Chinese Hospital - Peking, Chihli, 1914 (Box 19, Folder 316)
    - 115. Japanese Hospital - Peking, Chihli, 1914 (Box 19, Folder 317)
    - 116. Peking University - Peking, Chihli, 1914-17 (Box 19, Folder 318)
      Union University
    - 117. Government Medical College - Peking, Chihli, 1914-15 (Box 19, Folder 319)
    - 118. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Shuntefu, Chihli, 1915-18 (Box 19, Folder 320)
    - 119. Isabella Fisher Hospital - Tientsin, Chihli, 1914-17 (Box 19, Folder 321)
    - 120. Peiyang Medical School and Hospital - Tientsin, Chihli, 1914-16 (Box 19, Folder 322)
      Under Viceroy
    - 121. Tientsin Hospital - Tientsin, Chihli Tientsin, Chihli, 1914-16 (Box 19, Folder 323)
    - 122. Army Medical College - Tientsin, Chihlientsin, Chihli, 1914-16 (Box 19, Folder 324)
    - 123. London Missionary Society Hospital - Tsangchow, Chihli, 1914-18 (Box 19, Folder 325)
    - 124. American Board Mission Hospital - Tungchow, Chihli, 1914-18 (Box 19, Folder 326)
    - 125. Reformed Church in American Mission Hospital - Amoy, Fukien, 1914-18 (Box 19, Folder 327)
    - 126. English Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Changpu, Fukien, 1914 (Box 19, Folder 328)
    - 127. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Nansuchow, Anwhei, 1915-17 (Box 19, Folder 329)
    - 128. English Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Tsuenchaufu, Fukien, 1914 (Box 19, Folder 330)
    - 130. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Foochow, Fukien, 1914-15 (Box 19, Folder 331)
    - 131. American Board Mission Hospital - Foochow, Fukien, 1914-17 (Box 19, Folder 332)
    - 132. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Foochow, Fukien, 1914-15 (Box 19, Folder 333)
      Magew Memorial Hospital
    - 133. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Foochow, Fukien, 1915 (Box 19, Folder 334)
      Woolston Memorial Hospital
    - 134. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Funing, Fukien, 1914 (Box 19, Folder 335)
    - 135. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Futsing, Fukien, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 336)
    - 136. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Haiteng, Fukien, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 337)
    - 137. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Hinghwa, Fukien, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 338)
    - 138. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Hinghwa, Fukien, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 339)
    - 139. American Board Mission Hospital - Inghok, Fukien, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 340)
    - 140. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Kienning, Fukien, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 341)
    - 141. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Kutien, Fukien, 1914-15 (Box 20, Folder 342)
    - 142. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Mintsinghsien, Fukien, 1914-18 (Box 20, Folder 343)
    - 143. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Ngucheng, Fukien, 1914-15 (Box 20, Folder 344)
    - 144. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Nighteh, Fukien, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 345)
    - 145. American Board Mission Hospital - Shaowu, Fukien, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 346)
    - 146. Methodist Episcopal Hospital (North) - Sienyu, Fukien, 1914-15 (Box 20, Folder 347)
    - 147. Reformed Church in America Mission Hospital - Siokhe, Fukien, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 348)
    - 148. London Missionary Society Hospital - Tingchow, Fukien, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 349)
    - 149. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Yenping, Fukien, 1914-18 (Box 20, Folder 350)
    - 150. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Yungan, Fukien, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 351)
    - 151. English Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Yngchun, Fukien, 1916 (Box 20, Folder 352)
    - 152. Canadian Prebyterian Mission Hospitals - Honan, 1915-17 (Box 20, Folder 353)
    - 153. Roman Catholic Hospital - Chumatien, Honan, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 354)
    - 154. China Inland MIssioin Hospital - Kaifeng, Honan, 1914-17 (Box 20, Folder 355)
    - 155. Government Hospital - Kaifeng, Honan, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 356)
    - 156. Army Hospital - Kaifeng, Honan, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 357)
    - 157. American Lutheran Mission Hospital - Kioshan, Honan, 1914-17 (Box 20, Folder 358)
    - 158. Honan Province, 1915 (Box 20, Folder 359)
    - 159. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Changteh, Hunan, 1915-18 (Box 20, Folder 360)
    - 160. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Changteh, Hunan - reprints (Box 20, Folder 361)
    - 161. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Chenchow, Hunan, 1914-16 (Box 20, Folder 362)
    - 162. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Hengchow, Hunan, 1914-16 (Box 20, Folder 363)
    - 163. Wesleyan Methodist Mission Hospital - Pingkiang, Hunan, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 364)
    - 164. Reformed Church of the U.S. Mission Hospital - Shenchow, Hunan, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 365)
    - 165. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Siangtan, Hunan, 1914-18 (Box 20, Folder 366)
    - 166. Reformed Church in the U.S. Mission Hospital - Yochow, Hunan, 1914-16 (Box 20, Folder 367)
    - 167. Wesleyan Methodist Mission Hospital - Yungchow, Hunan, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 368)
    - 168. Hupeh Province, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 369)
    - 169. Wesleyan Methodist Mission Hospital - Anlu, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 370)
    - 170. Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Hankow, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 371)
    - 171. Cantonese Hospital - Hankow, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 372)
      Merchants Hospital
    - 172. International Hospital - Hankow, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 373)
      Foreign Concessions
    - 173. London Missionary Society Hospital - Hankow, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 374)
    - 174. Roman Catholic Hospital - Hankow, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 375)
    - 175. Wesleyan Methodist Mission Hospital - Hankow, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 376)
    - 176. Union Medical College and Hospital - Hankow, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 377)
    - 177. Japanese Hospital - Hankow, Hupehw, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 378)
      Japanese Concession
    - 178. American Baptist Mission Hospital (North) - Hanyang, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 379)
    - 179. Hanyang Iron and Steel Works - Hanyang, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 380)
      Private Company
    - 180. Roman Catholic Hospital - Laohokow, Hupeh, 1915 (Box 20, Folder 381)
    - 181. London Missionary Society Hospital - Siaokan, Hupeh, 1914-16 (Box 20, Folder 382)
    - 182. Wesleyan Methodist Mission Hospital - Tayeh, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 383)
    - 183. Wesleyan Methodist Mission Hospital - Teian, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 384)
    - 184. London Missionary Society Hospital - Tsaoshih, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 385)
    - 185. American Church Mission Hospital - Wuchang, Hupeh, 1914-18 (Box 20, Folder 386)
    - 186. London Missionary Society Hospital - Wuchang, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 387)
    - 187. Hupeh Medical Special College - Wuchang, Hupeh, 1914-15 (Box 20, Folder 388)
      Chinese
    - 188. Boone University Medical School - Wuchang, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 389)
    - 189. Wesleyan Methodist Mission Hospital - Wuchang, Hupeh, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 390)
    - 190. China Inland Mission Hospital - Lanchow, Kansu, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 391)
    - 191. Boone University - Wuchang, Hupeh, 1916-17 (Box 21, Folder 392)
    - 192. Fukien Christian University - Foochow, Fukien, 1914-18 (Box 21, Folder 393)
    - 194. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Kiukiang, Kiangsi, 1914-16 (Box 21, Folder 394)
    - 195. China Inland Mission Hospital - Jaochow, Kiangsi, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 395)
    - 196. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Kiukiang, Kiangsi, 1914-18 (Box 21, Folder 396)
    - 197. Red Cross Hospital - Kiukiang, Kiangsi, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 397)
    - 198. Roman Catholic Hospital - Kiukiang, Kiangsi, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 398)
    - 199. Insane Hospital - Kiukiang, Kiangsi, 1914-18 (Box 21, Folder 399)
    - 200. Kuling Medical Missionary Laboratory - Kuling, Kiangsi, 1914-15 (Box 21, Folder 400)
      Union
    - 201. Kuling Library - Kuling, Kiangsi, 1915 (Box 21, Folder 401)
    - 202. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Nanchang, Kiangsi, 1914-15 (Box 21, Folder 402)
    - 203. Army Hospital - Nanchang, Kiangsi, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 403)
    - 204. Medical School and Private Hospital - Nanchang, Kiangsi, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 404)
    - 205. Police Hospital - Nanchang, Kiangsi, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 405)
    - 206. Southern Baptist Convention Mission Hospital - Chengchow, Honan, 1914-18 (Box 21, Folder 406)
    - 207. London Missionary Hospital - Siaochang, Chihli, 1916-17 (Box 21, Folder 407)
    - 208. London Missionary Society Hospital - Tientsin, Chilhi, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 408)
    - 209. Foreign Christian Missionary Society Hospital - Batang, Szecwan, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 409)
    - 235. China Inland Mission Hospital - Chinkiang, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 410)
    - 236. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Chinkiang, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 411)
    - 238. Chinese Hospital - Nanking, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 412)
    - 239. Presbyterian Mission Training School for Nurses (North) - Nanking, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 413)
    - 240. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Nanking, Kiangsu, 1914-17 (Box 21, Folder 414)